{
    "id": "18ac08c90c3543b589fb6d1a979984ed",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This painting is older ……………………. that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "85d76d4dd35a44f69386cc38cfc0ee42"
        },
        {
            "question": "How is this different …………………….. that?",
            "description": "Different can be followed by from, to or than.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "to",
                "than",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "4167766a575c477aa107e0894ab9d6e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that boy …………………… the blue shirt?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6cb4f55c178b4497b1d537c7a057c105"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am waiting ……………………….. a call from my mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "of",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "53990895eadc428497bf772e81e7fa10"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly it occurred ……………………. me that I hadn’t locked the door.",
            "description": "If something occurs to you, you suddenly remember it.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2bb38b1c6e0c4b6bac10d176ea0f0234"
        },
        {
            "question": "She insisted …………………….. my joining her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9780864177fe43af8857f4c27d7ad174"
        },
        {
            "question": "He abstains ……………………… smoking and drinking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "87e913ffdddc42b196912a674986cc60"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must refrain ……………………… binge eating.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0437c6e1dc604f1cadd8a985fce443a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some rogues had set the house ………………………. fire.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6bb9d992ec14409cb974ea69c7f72153"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am thinking ……………………….. quitting my job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "over",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d579155d34324689bb37a95992919cef"
        },
        {
            "question": "His friends egged ……………………… him to run faster and faster.",
            "description": "To egg on somebody is to encourage them.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6c2f5c776d348ddb2a3632eb29326fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nothing could stop him ……………………… pursuing his goal.",
            "description": "Stop is followed by object + from.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "from",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "652ee857358f422b8b957d3793becbc1"
        }
    ]
}